{
    "id": "3979a9c2bcff448792afc71b0a4ec179",
    "title": "Gerund Or Infinitive",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I prefer walking ...................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to ride",
                "riding",
                "to riding"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "04b266d987d048cdb8106966dba9a61a"
        },
        {
            "question": "She enjoys ...................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to swim",
                "swimming"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3b6bfceb49b542f0b6d24abb41ade5d7"
        },
        {
            "question": "I want ....................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to leave",
                "leaving"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b4a68ed48a084b65b10acfc5fd989a81"
        },
        {
            "question": "Your hair needs ......................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to wash",
                "washing"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7afadab0edb944f0b719c008c12db44f"
        },
        {
            "question": "I am not used .......................................... four wheelers.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to drive",
                "to driving",
                "driving"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e9e321cf148b4edbb75d6726b53dabd7"
        },
        {
            "question": "Do you mind ....................................... here?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "me to sit",
                "my sitting",
                "me sitting"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "db267483b2da4cc793b4fe9b3493a9cf"
        },
        {
            "question": "I look forward ...................................... you at Easter.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to see",
                "at seeing",
                "to seeing"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "d18764b2115e45d9ad75208a747f7d73"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is used ......................................... hard.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to work",
                "to working",
                "working"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "82d85b09df53486cb81551694b3c99f4"
        },
        {
            "question": "I remember ....................................... butterflies when I was younger.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to chase",
                "chasing"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "15dc92069584470aacbecfe2a6b8b7d8"
        },
        {
            "question": "Little girls enjoy ........................................... with their balls.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to play",
                "playing"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3dbbd40b340b4a4ea2bdd0e2933826e0"
        },
        {
            "question": "Would you mind ........................................ a bit?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to move",
                "to moving",
                "moving"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "d268fcd81e4941df9e4782d18651530e"
        },
        {
            "question": "Donâ€™t forget .......................................... the letter.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "posting",
                "to post"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7f2fb4ec36704fb9a79acaed5dbe1ea8"
        }
    ]
}